[Plot Love II]
[مؤامرة الحب الثاني]
[Episode 12]
[الحلقة 12]
I didn't expect you to
لم أتوقع منك
ask me out for dinner.
اسألني لتناول العشاء.
I just want to find someone to talk to me.
أريد فقط أن أجد من يتحدث معي.
Because of Lu Nan?
بسبب لو نان؟
In fact, I feel that Lu Nan
في الواقع ، أشعر أن لو نان
is different from many rich people.
يختلف عن كثير من الأغنياء.
He defended you domineeringly
لقد دافع عنك باستبداد
in front of everyone at the birthday party that day.
أمام الجميع في حفلة عيد الميلاد في ذلك اليوم.
We all envied you.
كلنا نحسدك.
Well.
نحن سوف.
Some things cannot be judged
لا يمكن الحكم على بعض الأشياء
only on the surface.
فقط على السطح.
What do you mean?
ماذا تقصد بذلك؟
In fact,
في الواقع،
this is not Lu Nan's fault.
هذا ليس خطأ لو نان.
I didn't know grandma couldn't take honey.
لم أكن أعرف أن الجدة لا تستطيع تناول العسل.
I added honey to her tea.
أضفت العسل إلى شايها.
But it's not your fault.
لكن هذا ليس خطأك.
You didn't know it.
أنت لا تعرف ذلك.
But it's more than that.
لكن الأمر أكثر من ذلك.
Grandma wants me to be at home
الجدة تريد مني أن أكون في المنزل
to serve my husband and children.
لخدمة زوجي وأولادي.
But I don't want to give up my career.
لكني لا أريد أن أتخلى عن مسيرتي.
And it's impossible for me and Lu Nan at all.
وهذا مستحيل بالنسبة لي ولوان نان على الإطلاق.
But
ولكن
why can't a woman have her own career?
لماذا لا يمكن للمرأة أن يكون لها حياتها المهنية؟
Tell me.
أخبرني.
Women can only take care of children at home?
يمكن للمرأة فقط رعاية الأطفال في المنزل؟
You did nothing wrong about this.
أنت لم تفعل شيئًا خاطئًا حيال هذا.
Why are they asking you that?
لماذا يطلبون منك ذلك؟
I am in favor of you.
أنا أؤيدك.
Why are you more excited than me?
لماذا أنت متحمس أكثر مني؟
I...
أنا...
I just can't accept someone
أنا فقط لا أستطيع قبول شخص ما
planning your life
التخطيط لحياتك
in the name of love.
في اسم الحب.
You mean your brother?
تقصد اخوك؟
I remember when we first met,
أتذكر عندما التقينا لأول مرة ،
your brother
أخوك
sent someone
أرسل شخص ما
to take you back, right?
لإعادتك ، أليس كذلك؟
Yes.
نعم.
He recently chased me to Nanxi City.
لقد طاردني مؤخرًا إلى مدينة Nanxi.
We met
التقينا
and quarreled.
وتشاجروا.
Cheers.
هتافات.
Cheers to friendship.
في صحتك للصداقة.
Su Bei.
مع باي.
You are my first friend in Nanxi City.
أنت صديقي الأول في مدينة نانشي.
I recognize you.
تعرفت عليك.
Yes.
نعم.
If anyone dares to bully you in the future,
إذا تجرأ أي شخص على التنمر عليك في المستقبل ،
I will beat him up.
سوف أضربه.
Hey.
يا.
What a poor drinker.
يا له من شارب فقير.
You just drank a little.
لقد شربت قليلا.
I haven't had enough of it yet.
لم يكن لدي ما يكفي منه حتى الآن.
Lu Nan.
لو نان.
[I am at Evermore Bar, come pick me up.]
[أنا في إيفرمور بار ، تعال واصطحبني.]
Why is she so drunk?
لماذا هي في حالة سكر؟
She's unhappy.
إنها غير سعيدة.
Unhappy?
تعيس؟
By the way, you are...?
بالمناسبة ، أنت ...؟
I am Ye Ting, Su Bei's friend.
أنا يي تينج ، صديق Su Bei.
I will leave her to you.
سأتركها لك.
Okay, thanks.
حسنا شكرا.
Oops.
أُووبس.
I just cared about Su Bei
لقد اهتممت للتو بـ Su Bei
and forgot to mention the interview.
ونسيت ذكر المقابلة.
Ye Ting.
أيها تينغ.
I'll tell you a secret.
سأخبرك سرا.
Actually,
في الحقيقة،
I'm not the president's wife.
أنا لست زوجة الرئيس.
You asked me if I am doing well.
لقد سألتني إذا كنت بخير.
Auntie Lan also asked me if I am doing well.
سألتني العمة لان أيضًا إذا كنت بخير.
He's actually nice to me.
هو في الحقيقة لطيف معي.
He treats me well.
يعاملني جيدا.
But...
ولكن...
We are in a contractual relationship.
نحن في علاقة تعاقدية.
Humm...
همم...
Su Bei.
مع باي.
I'm not being nice to you
أنا لست لطيفًا معك
because of our contractual relationship.
بسبب علاقتنا التعاقدية.
You liar!
أنت كاذب!
I am not lying.
أنا لا أكذب.
You are!
أنت!
I never break my promise.
أنا لا أخلف بوعدى أبدا.
I don't believe in you.
أنا لا أؤمن بك.
Okay.
تمام.
What do I need to do
ما الذي أنا بحاجة لفعله
for you to believe me?
لكي تصدقني
You...
أنت...
I feel sick.
أشعر بالمرض.
Why did you drink so much?
لماذا شربت كثيرا؟
It's all because of you.
كله بسببك.
Because of me?
بسببي؟
Yes.
نعم.
I...
أنا...
Why am I here?
لماذا انا هنا؟
I let you go this time.
لقد سمحت لك بالذهاب هذه المرة.
If you get drunk again,
إذا شربت مرة أخرى ،
I'm not sure what will happen.
لست متأكدًا مما سيحدث.
Feier, here you are.
Feier ، ها أنت ذا.
Brother.
أخ.
I brought you breakfast.
أحضرت لك الإفطار.
Let's go back to see grandma after eating.
دعنا نعود لرؤية الجدة بعد الأكل.
Is grandma okay?
هل الجدة بخير؟
Is she feeling well?
هل هي بخير؟
What a smell of wine.
يا لها من رائحة النبيذ.
Sorry.
آسف.
I drank too much with my friend yesterday.
شربت كثيرا مع صديقي أمس.
Sister-in-law is also here.
أخت الزوج هنا أيضا.
Come back with us.
تعال معنا.
I...
أنا...
It's okay.
حسنا.
Grandma wasn't feeling well yesterday,
الجدة لم تكن على ما يرام أمس ،
so her attitude was kind of bad.
لذلك كان موقفها سيئًا نوعًا ما.
She must be very happy
يجب أن تكون سعيدة جدا
when you come back with us today.
عندما تعود معنا اليوم.
Hangover?
دوار من اثر الخمرة؟
Were you sad because of my words?
هل كنت حزينا بسبب كلامي؟
Drinking alcohol is not good for girls.
شرب الكحول ليس جيدًا للفتيات.
Why don't you
لماذا لا
take care of yourself?
اعتنِ بنفسك؟
Grandma.
الجدة.
Bei rarely drinks.
نادرا ما يشرب باي.
Yesterday was an exception.
أمس كان استثناء.
Drinking alcohol is a taboo during preparation for pregnancy.
يعتبر شرب الكحول من المحرمات أثناء التحضير للحمل.
Feier.
احتفال.
Make an appointment with Dr. Li.
حدد موعدًا مع دكتور لي.
Take this opportunity
أغتنم هذه الفرصة
to prepare Su Bei with a medical examination.
لتحضير Su Bei بالفحص الطبي.
Grandma, you are thinking too much.
جدتي ، أنت تفكر كثيرًا.
And I have no plans to have a baby for now.
وليس لدي أي خطط لإنجاب طفل في الوقت الحالي.
I have been very busy with work these years.
لقد كنت مشغولا جدا بالعمل هذه السنوات.
Even if I have a baby,
حتى لو كان لدي طفل ،
I don't have time to take care of him.
ليس لدي وقت للاعتناء به.
But I have
لكن لدي
plenty of time.
الكثير من الوقت.
I can't even
لا أستطيع حتى
get Su Bei checked now?
الحصول على فحص Su Bei الآن؟
Grandma.
الجدة.
Okay, grandma.
حسنًا ، جدتي.
It's all up to you.
الامر يرجع لك.
Mr. Lu.
السيد.  شمس.
The top three places in the municipal competition have been announced.
تم الإعلان عن المراكز الثلاثة الأولى في مسابقة البلدية.
Our company's Chen Shaojie is the third.
شركتنا Chen Shaojie هي الثالثة.
The first is Mrs. Lu.
الأول هو السيدة لو.
The first?
الأول؟
As expected of my wife.
كما هو متوقع من زوجتي.
Book a fine restaurant.
احجز مطعمًا جيدًا.
I'm going to celebrate for Bei.
سأحتفل من أجل باي.
Okay.
تمام.
Remember to prepare cake and flowers.
تذكر تحضير الكيك والزهور.
Got it.
فهمتك.
[Congratulations on winning the first place in the competition.]
[مبروك فوزك بالمركز الأول في المسابقة].
[Thanks.]
[شكرًا.]
[I booked a restaurant to celebrate for you at night.]
[لقد حجزت مطعمًا للاحتفال من أجلك بالليل.]
[Sorry, I have made an appointment with someone else at night.]
[آسف ، لقد حددت موعدًا مع شخص آخر في الليل.]
Mr. Lu, what's up?
السيد لو ، ما الأمر؟
Find out who is Su Bei going to meet tonight.
تعرف على من ستلتقي Su Bei الليلة.
Gosh.
يا الهي.
Mrs. Lu made an appointment with someone else at night?
السيدة لو حددت موعدًا مع شخص آخر في الليل؟
Then the cake and flowers I just ordered...
ثم الكعكة والزهور التي طلبتها للتو ...
Take them.
خذهم.
Cheers.
هتافات.
Congratulations on your first place.
مبروك على المركز الأول الخاص بك.
It's just a municipal competition.
إنها مجرد مسابقة بلدية.
The next games will be more and more difficult.
ستكون المباريات القادمة أكثر صعوبة.
It's okay, I believe in you.
لا بأس ، أنا أؤمن بك.
What's going on?
ماذا يحدث هنا؟
♪Another♪
♪ آخر ♪
♪Long talk all night♪
♪ حديث طويل طوال الليل ♪
♪I haven't finished drinking the water on the table♪
لم أنتهي من شرب الماء على المائدة
♪I stare at the windowsill♪
أحدق في حافة النافذة
♪That fallen flower is no longer blooming♪
♪ تلك الزهرة الساقطة لم تعد تتفتح
♪You always say♪
♪ أنت دائما تقول ♪
♪Like and love♪
♪ اعجاب وحب ♪
♪Are similar but different♪
♪ متشابهة لكنها مختلفة ♪
♪Finally this time I'm being depended on too♪
♪ أخيرًا هذه المرة أنا أعتمد أيضًا
♪Listen and cover up, learn to sigh♪
♪ استمع وتستر وتعلم التنهد ♪
♪How happy you are laughing♪
♪ ما مدى سعادتك بالضحك
♪You are planning your future with her♪
♪ أنت تخططين لمستقبلك معها
♪I'm so numb, but I'm♪
♪ أنا مخدر جدًا ، لكنني ♪
♪Still listening♪
♪ ما زلت تستمع ♪
♪I don't have to guess your mind anymore♪
♪ ليس عليّ أن أخمن عقلك بعد الآن ♪
♪Is it funny, sad or helpless♪
♪ هل هو مضحك أم حزين أم عاجز ♪
♪Adults shouldn't lose their temper easily♪
♪ لا ينبغي أن يفقد البالغون أعصابهم بسهولة ♪